{
    "subject": "resource/Erich_Mende",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Mende, Erich",
    "human_readable": "The name of Erich Mende is Mende, Erich.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9487826824188232,
            "question": "What is the full name of Erich Mende?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9269404411315918,
            "question": "Is 'Mende' Erich Mende's given name or surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9149967432022095,
            "question": "What is the last name of Erich Mende?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8816995620727539,
            "question": "What is the first name of Erich Mende?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8404152989387512,
            "question": "What order do the names appear in Erich Mende's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947763204574585,
            "question": "If you were to introduce Erich Mende, what would you say his full name was?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7640853524208069,
            "question": "How is Erich Mende's name written in reverse order?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7055918574333191,
            "question": "How many parts make up Erich Mende's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5673229694366455,
            "question": "Is 'Erich' a common first or last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3687835931777954,
            "question": "Would you spell 'Mende' with an accent?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Erich Mende is Mende, Erich.",
            "html": "dbpedia_645_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Erich' a common first or last name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_645_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many parts make up Erich Mende's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_645_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Erich Mende's name written in reverse order?",
            "html": "dbpedia_645_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_645_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about a person named Erich Mende, including his full name and dates of birth and death. Therefore, the statement \"The name of Erich Mende is Mende, Erich\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}